nbplc.com 2017-05-27

# NBPlc - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

NIGERIAN BREWERIES PLC (Henceforth referenced as “NB”) is the controller of the processing of all personal data collected through the Website. NB respects your privacy and complies with all Nigerian Laws regarding the collection and protection of consumer data.

NB does not collect or process personal data through the cookies placed by NB. NB only processes personal data that a user voluntarily provides to NB, by filling out a form for a service provided by the NB. This information may include such user’s first and last name, e-mail address, date of birth and state of residence.

##### Special Notice - if you are under 18 years old

Our website is not aimed at anyone under the age of 18 (Nigeria’s age of legal consent). All who access the site are required to declare themselves above 18 through the age gate. We therefore ask any individuals accessing the site who are under the age of 18 to cease and also to not provide any personal information via this or any other NB sites. 

##### Purposes of the collection of your data 

One of the purposes of our website is to inform you of who we are and what we do. We collect and use personal information (including name, address, telephone number and email) to better provide you with the required services, or information. We would therefore use your personal information in order to:  
• respond to queries or requests submitted by you   
• process orders or applications submitted by you   
• administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us   
• anticipate and resolve problems with any goods or services supplied to you   
• create products or services that may meet your needs. 

To optimize our services we may wish to use your personal data for direct marketing. As we respect your privacy we will only use your personal data for this purpose when you are aware thereof and if required we will request your consent prior to using your personal data for direct marketing.

Additionally, if at any time you wish us to stop using your information for any or all of the above purposes, please contact us as set out below. We will stop the use of your information for such purposes as soon as it is reasonably possible to do so.  
In addition, the collected personal data will (occasionally) be transferred to selected third parties, as part of the services offered to you through our site. These third parties will not use your personal information for any other purposes than what we have agreed with them. NB requests those third parties to implement adequate levels of protection in order to safeguard your personal information.

Except as set out in this privacy policy, we will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your permission unless we are legally entitled or required to do so (for example, if required to do so by legal process or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime) or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and/or defend our rights, property or personal safety and those of our users/customers or other individuals.  
Please be assured that we will not use your information for any of the purposes if you have indicated that you do not wish us to use your information in this way when submitting the information or at a later stage.

##### Collection of non-personal information

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the website from which you linked to our website. We may also aggregate details which you have submitted to the site (for example, your age and the town where you live). You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on this web site. We may from time to time supply third parties with this non-personal or aggregated data for uses in connection with this website.

**Security of your personal data**  
We have implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use and will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate.

##### Use of your personal information submitted to other web sites

On our websites, we may have links to other websites or you are referred to our website through a link from another website. As you can imagine, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites. Such content is subject to their terms of use and any additional guidelines and privacy information provided in relation to that use on their website.

We recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit to better understand your rights and obligations especially when you are submitting any type of content on those third party website. Please contact the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions.

##### Cookies policy

We use the term “cookies” to refer to cookies and other similar technologies described below  
Cookies are small data files that your browser places on your computer or device.  Cookies help your browser navigate a website and the cookies themselves cannot collect any information stored on your computer or your files.  
When a server uses a web browser to read cookies they can help a website deliver a more user-friendly service. To protect your privacy, your browser only gives a website access to the cookies it has already sent to you.

##### Why do we use cookies?

We use cookies to learn more about the way you interact with our content and help us to improve your experience when visiting our website.

Cookies remember the type of browser you use and which additional browser software you have installed. They also remember your preferences, such as language and region, which remain as your default settings when you revisit the website. Cookies also allow you to rate pages and fill in comment forms.

Some of the cookies we use are session cookies and only last until you close your browser, others are persistent cookies which are stored on your computer for longer.  For further details on the various types of cookies that we use, please read our [cookie policy](https://www.shell.com.ng/about-our-website/privacy-policy/cookie-policy.html).

##### How are third party cookies used? 

For some of the functions within our websites we use third party suppliers, for example, when you visit a page with videos embedded from or links to YouTube. These videos or links (and any other content from third party suppliers) may contain third party cookies and you may wish to consult the policies of these third party websites for information regarding their use of cookies. For further details on the third party cookies that we use, please read our page on [cookie types](https://www.shell.com.ng/about-our-website/privacy-policy/cookie-policy/cookie-type.html).

##### How do I reject and delete cookies? 

We will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. However, should you wish to do so, you can choose to reject or block the cookies set by NB or the websites of any third party suppliers by changing your browser settings – see the Help function within your browser for further details. Please note that most browsers automatically accept cookies so if you do not wish cookies to be used you may need to actively delete or block the cookies.

You can also visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.shell.com.ng/disclaimer-en.html/aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGxhYm91dGNvb2tpZXMub3JnLw==) for details on how to delete or reject cookies and for further information on cookies generally. For information on the use of cookies in mobile phone browsers and for details on how to reject or delete such cookies, please refer to your handset manual.

Note, however, that if you reject the use of cookies you will still be able to visit our websites but some of the functions may not work correctly.

##### Changes to this policy

From time to time we may make changes to this privacy policy. If we make any substantial changes to this privacy policy and the way in which we use your personal data we will post these changes on this page and will do our best to notify you of any significant changes. Please check our privacy policy on a regular basis.

##### How can you contact us?

If you would like to contact us about our privacy policy, you can do so by emailing us at info@nbplc.com
